谢谢你们赶过来
Thanks for coming by.
我们希望你们能帮我们想一些婚礼上用的点子
We wanted to bounce some ideas off of you about the wedding ceremony.
-怎么了? 你还好吗? -那只是因为…
- What's the matter? Are you okay? - It's just...
莫妮卡说了“婚礼”
Monica said, "wedding."
我们希望你们之中有人能上台念些东西
We thought one of you could read something.
我爱念诗
I would love to read a poem.
你认为你能念完一首诗?
Do you think you could get through a poem?
短篇
A short one.
好吧，那罗斯来读
Okay, so Ross will be doing the reading.
好的，我想我也能胜任
Okay, yeah, I guess I can do that too.
也能?
Too?
我自己想了一个点子，来庆祝你们的婚礼
I kind of have something else planned for you guys.
-你能告诉我们是什么点子吗? -抱歉
- Do you mind telling us what it is? - Sorry.
我想把它当成高度机密
I'm kind of keeping this one on the q. T.
不管你是指哪个，我希望包括眨眼睛
Whatever it is, I hope it involves winking.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我跟《我日》的编剧谈过…
I talked to one of the DOOL writers...
-什么是《我日》? -《我们的日子》
- What is DOOL? - Days of Our Lives.
你们一定不相信 我演的角色就要醒过来了
You're not gonna believe it. My character is coming out of his coma!
-那真的是太棒了 -哇，乔伊
- That's wonderful. - Wow, Joey.
不只是那个，我会有个新脑子!
And not only that, I'm getting a new brain!
你的工作跟私生活都有了很棒的进展
So great things are happening at work and in your personal life.
你要换个新脑子?
You're getting a new brain?
他们要杀死剧中一个角色…
They're killing off one of the characters on the show...
将她的脑子移植到我的身体里
...and her brain is being transplanted into my body.
什么? 脑部移植手术?
What? A brain transplant?
是的，这是最有争议的手术
Yes, it's a highly controversial procedure.
这太可笑了
It's ridiculous.
可笑的是你三个半月没有做过爱
It's ridiculous that you haven't had sex in three and a half months.
现在是冬天，街上的人少了很多
It's winter. There are fewer people on the street.
他们要杀谁?
Who are they killing off?
西西雅梦露，她饰演洁西卡拉哈特
Cecilia Monroe. She plays Jessica Lockhart.
不!
No!
她是《我日》里我最喜欢的角色了
She's my favorite character on DOOL.
不错
Nice.
她最擅长将饮料泼到别人脸上
She is so good at throwing drinks in people's faces.
我从来没看过她喝完一杯饮料
I don't think I've ever seen her finish a beverage.
还有她打人巴掌的样子，你不想那么做吗?
The way she slaps people. Wouldn't you love to do that?
不要乱来
Don't do it.
-西西雅梦露，多好的演员啊 -没错
- Cecilia Monroe, what a great actress. - Tell me about it.
她参与这部戏的演出很久了
And she's been on the show forever.
要代替她一定很难
It's gonna be really hard to fill her shoes.
你帮我解释一下
Help me out here.
当你做过“脑部移植”手术后…
When you come out of the brain transplant...
你要变成她?
...you are going to be her?
对，但是在德瑞克的身体里
Yes, but in Drake Ramoray's body.
你为什么就是搞不懂? 我还以为你是科学家
Why is this so hard for you to get? I thought you were a scientist.
Friends  S07E15 乔伊的新大脑
The One With Joey's New Brain
瑞秋，那边那个男的…
Rach, so that guy there...
异性恋还是同性恋?
...straight or gay?
应该是同性恋
Well, I'd have to say gay.
是吗? 为什么?
Yeah? Why?
主要是因为他在亲别的男人
Mainly because he's kissing that other guy.
不，不是那个男人，是这个男人
Oh, no, not that guy there. That guy right there.
他太帅了，不可能是异性恋
Oh, yeah, he's too cute to be straight.
大波霸会帮我们查个清楚
Knockers will help us figure it out.
好了，他是异性恋
All right, straight.
而且一眼就看得出来
And not subtle.
他忘了拿手机
He left his cell phone.
我们得把它交给甘瑟，放在失物招领处
We could hand it to Gunther to put it in lost and found.
或是用它打电话到中国看看那些人在做什么?
Or we could use it to call China, see how those guys are doing.
如果他打电话来找手机，我接了电话…
What if he calls his own cell phone and I answer...
我们开始聊天，之后坠入爱河呢?
...and we start talking and we fell in love?
那是个很棒的故事吧?
Wouldrt that be a great story?
就像是数字时代的童话故事
Kind of like a fairy tale for the digital age.
那听起来很棒，我要去拿手机
That does sound great. I'm gonna get the phone.
什么? 等一下 你为什么要得到这个故事
What? Wait. Why do you get the story?
我已经很久没有约会了
I haven't been out on a date in so long.
菲比，三天前你才约过会
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
那不是约会，那只是朋友聚会，然后做爱
That wasn't a date. That was friends getting together and having sex.
好吧，我去拿手机
Okay. Great. I get the phone.
不行，一星期前你才跟泰格分手
No way. You just broke up with Tag a week ago.
对，直到现在，我本认为我不会再爱一次
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think I would love again.
-说的好 -等一下
- Nice try. - Wait.
我们该怎么公平地决定，谁能拿走手机呢?
How do we fairly decide who gets the phone?
我不知道
I don't know.
或许我们可以…
Maybe we could...
你动作太慢了!
Aha! Too slow!
你太自大了
Aha! Too cocky.
我在跟他约会，妈妈，你管不了
I'm dating him. There's nothing you can do.
不，我管得了
Yes, there is.
你打算怎么做? 杀了他吗？ 就像你杀了查尔斯?
What are you going to do, kill him? Like you did Charles?
那是意外
That was an accident.
你也好不到哪里去
And so were you.
至少我不是杀人犯
Well, at least I'm not a murderer.
我的宝贝
Oh, my baby.
停!
Cut!
你演得太好了，刚刚那一巴掌很逼真，你怎么办到的?
That was a great scene. That slap looked so real. How do you do that?
-那只是多年的经验 -快拿冰块过来给我
- Oh, just years of experience. - Can I get some ice here?!
我想说我觉得你的演技很棒
I just wanted to say how wonderful I think you are.
你该不会是那个快死掉的影迷吧?
You're not the fan who's dying, are you?
我要会见并拥抱一个快死的影迷
I'm supposed to meet and hug a fan who's dying.
但那不应该是以后的事吗
But that's not suppose to be until later.
我是乔伊崔比亚尼，昨天我们合拍过一场戏
I'm Joey Tribbiani. We did a scene together yesterday.
-我就是那个昏迷的人 -那是真人?
- I'm the guy in the coma. - Oh, that was a real person?
因为你离开后我要移植你的脑子…
Since I'm getting your brain when you leave the show...
我在想如果…
...I was wondering if...
-我要离开? -我不知道，为什么? 你听到了什么?
- I'm leaving the show?  -Why? Did you hear something?
是谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
-编剧之一 -哪个编剧? 是秃头佬还是高个子?
- One of the writers. - Which writer? Was it bald or was it tall?
那不重要，因为那不是真的
You know, it doesn't matter, because it is not true.
好吧
Okay.
如果那是真的，你竟然敢来叫我教你…
And if it were true, how dare you come to me and ask me for tips...
该如何饰演我演了二十年的角色
...about a character I've played for 20 years!
梦露小姐…哦，你真的那么做了
Miss Monroe... Oh, there you go.
不，菲比，你不能那样拿走电话 那不公平
No, Phoebe, you cannot get the phone that way. That's not fair.
好吧，听着，我有个点子
Okay, look, I have an idea.
我们为什么不看看他的速拨键记录了哪些电话号码，
Why don't we see what kind of numbers he has on his speed dial...
跟他有最多共通点的人，就可以把手机拿走
...and then whoever has more in common with him gets the phone.
或者看谁的名字最接近“电话”那个字（与“菲比”最接近）
Or we can decide by whoever's name is closer to the word "phone."
我不那样认为
I don't think so.
好吧．不过我肯定你还会继续跟我争论的
Fine.  But I bet you'd be singing a different tune if we were fighting over a ratchet.
速拨键的第一个名字是“妈妈”
First name on the speed dial is "Mom."
哦，我妈妈自杀死了
Oh. I lost my mom to suicide.
不行，你不能利用那一点抢走帅哥跟最后一块蓝莓松饼
No way. You can't use that to get the cute guy and the last blueberry muffin.
今天我已经用过那个借口了? 对不起
Did I use that already today? I'm sorry.
好了，你看，还没有结果
Well, now, see, this isn't telling us anything.
-“乔，卡洛斯，瑜伽，班” -等一下，我练瑜伽．那是我的
- "Joe. Carlos. Yoga. Ben..." - Wait. I do yoga. That's one for me.
好吧．哦，差一点，如果是“优格”就好了（酸奶酪）
Oh, all right. Oh, so close. If only it said, "yogurt."
“彼得・卢格尔”，那是牛排店
"Peter Luger." That's a steak house.
好吧，肉食者．这个是你的
Okay, fine. Meat-eater. Fine, that's one for you.
我赢了，他在速拨键里记下了巴尼斯
Oh, I win. He's got Barneys on his speed dial.
你不知道他指的是不是巴尼斯服饰店
You don't know it's Barneys the store.
那可能是他朋友家或是酒吧的电话…
That could be his friend's house or a bar...
谁会把巴尼斯服饰店的电话记录成速拨键?
Who has Barneys the store on their speed dial?
他的新女朋友
His new girlfriend.
那是什么声音?
What is that?
我想是快死掉的猫在举行游行
I think it's the Dying Cat Parade.
听起来是从对街传来的
Sounds like it's coming from across the street.
-我的天啊 -什么?
- Oh, my God. - What?
还记得罗斯说他要在婚礼上给我们惊喜吗?
The thing that Ross was gonna do at our wedding?
他跟我出去玩时说：“你有苏格兰的血统吧?”
He was hanging out with me and said, "You're half Scottish, right?"
-不 -是的!
- No. - Yes!
不，不可能，不可能是罗斯
No. There is no way. It cannot be Ross.
不可思议，为什么你有苏格兰血统?
Unbelievable. Why is your family Scottish?
为什么罗斯是你哥哥?
Why is your family Ross?
他不能在婚礼上演奏，大家都会跑光的
He cannot play at our wedding. Everyone will leave.
就好像指责我不守戒律（犹太教）
It'll be like when he rapped at my bat mitzvah.
不能跟他说不．他可能会练习一辈子的，那样他就完了
We can't just tell him no. He's probably been practicing forever. He'll be crushed.
也许有可以不伤害他感情的方法
Maybe there's a way we can tell him without hurting his feelings.
拜托，那只是噪音!
I mean, come on. That is just noise!
那根本不算是歌
It's not even a song.
等一下，如果你仔细听…
Wait. If you listen very carefully...
我想它是“库尔与伙伴”乐团唱的《庆祝》
...I think it's "Celebration" by Kool and the Gang.
-嗨，你好吗? -我很好
- Hi. How are you? - Good.
还记得我们在咖啡厅时…
Remember when we were in the coffeehouse...
我们决定我可以拿走那个帅哥的手机吗?
...we decided I was gonna keep the cute guy's phone?
我要把它放在我的皮包里 如果它响了，我就能立刻接听
I was gonna keep it in my purse so if it rang, I could just pick it up?
你还记得你从我的皮包把手机偷走了吗?
Do you remember going into my purse and stealing the phone?
我听不懂你在说什么?
Now you lost me.
-你偷走了手机 -不，我没有
- You stole the phone. - No, I didn't.
如果我拨号过去它不会响吗?
You're saying that if I called it, it wouldn't ring?
-不会 -好
- No. - Okay.
既然你要拨号了 我要让你看看我刚买的响铃皮包
But while you dial, let me show you the features of my new ringing handbag.
噢，它真的有用
Oh, it does work.
-菲比 -那是另一只手机
- Phoebe. - That is a different phone.
是吗? 喂，对，你好，瑞秋在吗?
Oh, is it? Hello. Yes, hi, is Rachel there?
她在，请稍等，是找我的
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please. It's for me!
那是铁证
That is damning evidence.
我的天哪，一定是他
Oh, my God. I bet that's him.
我的数字童话故事就要开始了
My digital fairy tale's about to begin.
该怎么样说呢? 就说“你好”?
I wonder how it should be? Should I be, "Hello"?
或者说，“嗨!我是瑞”?
Or should I be, "Hi! It's Ra..."?
你能不能别再那么做了?
Would you stop doing that?
喂，对，我就是捡到你手机的人
Hello? Yes, I'm the one who found your phone.
-菲比，你不能…-我在讲电话
- Phoebe, you can't... - I'm on a call.
对，今晚你能过来拿，就八点半吧?
Yeah, you can pick it up tonight. Say, 8:30?
到我家来
At my apartment.
摩顿街五号，十四号房
It's 5 Morton Street, apartment 14.
或许之后 我们可以去吃点东西或者其他什么的
And then maybe, you know, after, we can grab a bite to eat or whatever.
好的，到时候见，再见
Okay. Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
你知道 他来的时候我会在这里
You do know that I will be here when he comes over.
你怎么知道他什么时候会来?
How will you know what time to come over?
你刚刚说出来了
You just said it.
好吧，我希望到时我能一个人呆着
Well, I was kind of hoping that I would just be alone.
我要好好想想我母亲和她的自杀
You know, to think about my mom and her suicide.
-噢，菲比! -什么? 那是今天第一次说
- Oh, Phoebe! - What? That's the first time today.
你喜欢墨西哥玉米片?
So you like the nachos, huh?
-我自己，则喜欢…-我只有16岁
- Myself, I'm partial to... - I'm 16.
2003年见（此时是2001年，两年之后她就18岁成年了）
See you in 2003.
你说的对，他们要将我踢出这部戏
You're right. They are writing me out of the show.
他们还没有决定什么时候，但应该很快…
They don't know exactly when it's going to happen, but soon...
就是这样了
...and then that's it.
我真的很抱歉，如果我可以决定 你永远都不会离开这部戏
I'm so sorry. If it was up to me, you would never leave the show.
-谢谢你 -我是认真的
- Yeah, thanks. - I mean it.
我不敢相信他们会对你这么做 还有你的影迷
I can't believe they'd do this to you. And to your fans.
他们一定会崩溃伤心，他们是那么地爱你
They're gonna be devastated. Heartbroken. They love you so much.
你说的对
Oh, you're right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你说你叫什么名字?
What's your name again?
-乔伊 -谢谢你
- Joey. - Thank you.
那真的太贴心了
That is so sweet.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
-那不是我的决定 -我在跟别人说话呢
- It wasn't my decision. - I'm having a conversation here.
你接着说
You were saying.
听着，之前我会来找你
Look, the only reason I came up to you before...
是因为…
...is because, well...
因为要饰演你我真的很紧张
...l'm really nervous about being you.
请你帮我抓住角色的精髓
If you could help me capture the essence of the character, you know.
帮助我让洁西卡继续活下去，可以吗?
Help me keep Jessica alive. Please?
好吧，乔伊，我会帮你
All right, Joey, I'll help you.
不是因为我对这部蠢戏有亏欠…
Not because I owe it to this stupid show...
而是因为我亏欠洁西卡
...but because I owe it to Jessica.
-那真的是太棒了，谢谢你 -别客气
- Oh, that's great. Thank you so much. - You're so welcome.
我一直在看录影带，你觉得这样如何?
I've been watching some tapes. How's this?
洁西卡拉哈特永远都不会再踏入这里!
Jessica Lockhart will never step foot in this place again!
永远都不会!
Never!
-那是我吗? -没错
- Is that supposed to be me? - Yeah.
但洁西卡没有英国腔
But Jessica doesn't have an English accent.
我有英国腔?
I can do an English accent?
我要把这点写在我履历表里
That baby's going on my resume.
我想吃点点心
Well, I feel like a snack.
你要吃点脆饼吗? 它是你故乡苏格兰的点心
Do you want some shortbread? It's Scottish, like you are.
不，谢谢，我不喜欢任何苏格兰的东西
Oh, no, thanks. I don't like anything from my Scottish heritage.
什么?
What?
因为我的家族被赶出苏格兰…
Well, it's just that my entire family was run out of Scotland by...
是维京人干的
...Vikings.
总之，很多不好的回亿
Anyway, lots of bad memories.
听起来你家人准备要恢复苏格兰传统
It sounds to me like your family's ready to rediscover its Scottish roots.
不，不，他们不会的
No. No, they're not.
他们还非常愤怒
They're still very angry.
不过，你知道，钱德也有瑞典血统
But, you know, Chandler's also half-Swedish.
知道瑞典人以什么著称吗?
You know what the Swedish people are famous for?
安静的坐着
Sitting down and being quiet.
不过苏格兰历史非常…
Yeah, but the Scottish history is so much...
你不能在婚礼上吹风笛!
You can't play bagpipes at the wedding!
你们怎么知道?
How did you know about that?
-我们听到你在家里吹风笛 -是你们去报警的?
- We heard you play from your apartment. -Were you the ones who called the cops?
现在那真的不是最重要的部分
That's not really important right now.
重要的是，我们谢谢你的好意…
What is important is, while we appreciate the gesture...
我们只是觉得我们的婚礼上不适合吹风笛
...we just don't feel that bagpipes are appropriate for our wedding.
-为什么? -因为我们讨厌风笛
- Why not? - Because we hate them.
别这样，那不公平．你们还没听过我的演奏
Come on, that's not fair. You haven't even heard me play.
听过了
We have heard you play.
不，你们只是听过我练习而己
No, you've heard me practice.
给我机会为你们表演，再做最后的决定
Just give me a chance to perform for you, then decide whatever you want.
我也不会告诉你们，我要吹哪首曲子
I'm not gonna tell you what song I'm gonna play either.
只是说当表演结束后…
Let's just say when it's over...
我们一定会“庆祝”一下
...l'll bet there'll be a wee bit of celebration.
这个角色的精髓源自于她的自信
The essence of the character is rooted in her confidence.
譬如说，当洁西卡走进一个房间时…
So when Jessica enters a room, for instance...
她拥有那个房间里…
...she owns everything...
所有事物跟所有人
...and every person in that room.
-你来试试看 -好吧
- You try it. - Okay.
不错
All right!
不．他已经知道他拥有房间里的一切
No. He already knows that he owns everything in the room.
他不是第一次发现
He's not finding it out for the first time.
-再来试一次 -好的
- So try it again. - Okay.
他也没有对这个房间生气
He's not angry at the room either.
再试一次，他拥有它，他拥有这个房间
Try it again. He owns it. He owns the room.
这是他的，他拥有这个房间! 他拥有它!
It is his. He owns, owns, owns the room! He owns it!
这有点奇怪，但已经好多了
It's a little weird, but it's getting better.
我一定会想念这个女人 我不知道我该怎么办
I'm gonna miss this woman so much. I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我演这部戏二十年了
It's been 20 years of my life.
或许这是件好事
Hey, hey. Maybe this is a good thing.
它给你机会做改变 扮演不一样的角色
It'll give you a chance to shake things up. Play different characters.
你才华横溢
You're so talented.
是的，没错
I am, I am.
但是我不知道．你知道…
But I don't know. You know...
…上了年纪的演员，不容易啊
...an actor of a certain age, it's not that easy.
那不是真的，看看安洁拉・兰斯布（著名英国演员） 安吉丽娜・朱莉（奥斯卡最佳女配角）
That's not true. Look at Angela Lansbur... Angelina Jolie.
或许我该在几年前离开，那时候很多人要我接戏．
Probably should've just left years ago when the offers were pouring in...
但我在这里过得太舒服…
...but I just got so comfy here and...
我拒绝了一些大好机会
I turned down some amazing work.
譬如说呢?
Like what?
哦，就说如果我在十五年前离开…
Well, let's just say if I'd left 15 years ago...
现在墨西哥影坛会完全不一样
...the landscape of Mexican cinema would be very different today.
哇
Wow.
但现在…现在时机不一样了
But, well, now... Now's a different time for me.
嘿，别这样
Oh, hey, come on. Don't do this.
听我说句话，好吗?
Let me tell you something, okay?
当我看到你演戏时，我想“天啊，她是个很棒的演员”
When I watch you do a scene, I'm thinking, "Boy, she is a great actress."
但我也会想“她好辣”
But I'm also thinking, "She is hot."
你觉得我很辣?
You think I'm hot?
你拥有这个房间
You own the room.
或许我们应该…
We should probably get the...
对，我们应该…
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we should get...
当洁西卡吻男人时…
So when Jessica kisses a man...
她通常会把…
...she usually puts...
双手放在那个男人脸上
...both her hands on the man's face.
我注意到了，那是因为她充满了热情吗?
I notice that. Is that because she's so passionate?
不，那是因为那样子摄影机只能拍到她
No, it's because that way the camera only sees her.
你想试试看吗?
You want to try it?
好的
Yeah, okay.
太棒了，真的很不错
That was good. That was really good.
但我想你手的位置不对，它们应该…
But I think that maybe your hands are just a little off. They should be right...
嘿
Hey, hey!
是谁?
Who is it?
我是汤姆，我来拿手机的
It's Tom. I'm here to pick up the phone.
为什么要由你去开门?
Why do you get to answer the door?
-为什么不行? -因为这里是我家
- Why shouldn't I ? - Because it's my apartment.
那么由我来把手机交给他
Then I get to give him the cell phone.
好吧，希望你能好好跟他解释那些打到中国的电话
Okay. Good luck explaining all the calls to China.
嗨
Hi.
我们争执了多久?
Wow, how long were we arguing for?
你不是那个忘了拿手机的人
You're not the man who left the phone.
-对，他是我的助理 -他会来吗?
- No, that's my assistant. - Is he coming?
不会
No.
-你能让我们谈一下吗? -没问题
- Could you give us one second? - Sure.
我们马上回来，先生
We'll be right back, sir.
-我们该怎么办? -我不知道
- What do we do? - I don't know.
你能相信吗?
Can you believe this?
我们在等一个帅哥 结果来了一个超级大帅哥
We were waiting for a hot guy, and then an even hotter one shows up.
我知道
I know.
什么?
What?
他们不再喜欢那样了，知道吗?
They just don't make them like that anymore, you know?
不．他们喜欢．不过你要等待
No, they do, but you just have to wait.
瑞秋，听我说…
Rachel, listen...
如果你能把他让给我 我真的欠你一个大人情
...if you let me have him, then I will really owe you one.
好吧
All right.
好吧，我把他让给你
All right, I will let you have him.
但你欠我一个大人情
But you owe me. You owe me big.
好的，你真是好朋友
Yeah. You're such a great friend.
哪一位漂亮的小姐要陪我去吃晚餐?
Which one of you lovely ladies am I taking to dinner?
是我，先生
Oh, that'd be me, sir.
-你先请 -谢谢
- After you. - Oh, thank you.
太棒了
Nice.
你的确拥有那个房间
Well, you certainly own that room.
事实上我租下整间公寓 我刚了解你的意思，谢谢夸奖
Actually, I rent the whole place. I just got what you meant. Thank you.
-嗨 -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
洁西卡拉哈特! 在我家里面!
Oh, Jessica Lockhart! In my apartment!
我是你的头号大影迷，我是你的头号大影迷
I am such a huge fan. I am such a huge fan.
很高兴能知道…
It's nice to know...
莫妮卡!
Monica!
她是我的室友瑞秋
That's my roommate, Rachel.
难怪你家会有女人内衣
That explains all the womers underwear.
没错
Sure.
我的天啊，是真的!
Oh, my God, it's true!
我的天哪，你太迷人了
Oh, my God, you are so amazing.
我的天啊，我能请你帮我一个忙吗?
Can I just ask you to do me just one favor?
当然可以
Certainly.
你能打我一巴掌吗?
Would you slap me right here in the face?
我很乐意，但我的律师说 我不能再那么做了
I'd love to, but my lawyer said I can't do that anymore.
天哪，看上去你人真的非常好
God, you seem really, really nice.
好了，再见
Okay, bye-bye.
我是说，不像其他名人那样做作
I mean, not fake at all like most famous people.
好了，我们走
All right, here we go.
不，等一下，还有一件事
No, wait. Just one more thing.
-你是个笨女人 -我真的不能打你巴掌
- You're a stupid bitch. - I really can't slap you.
你真漂亮 很高兴见到你
- You are so beautiful. - So nice to meet you.
-我的天啊，你太棒了 -谢谢你们过来
- My God, you're great. - Thanks for stopping by.
-我真的很抱歉 -不
- I am so sorry about that. - Oh, no.
我习惯被影迷包围，别担心
Being adored, I'm used to it. Don't worry about it.
-我的天啊 -什么?
- Oh, my God. - What?
他们寄了今天的剧本来给我 他们从来没有寄剧本给过我
They sent me today's script. They never send me the script.
-是吗? -我一直都昏迷不醒
- They don't? - I'm just in a coma.
这代表我有台词了
This must mean I have lines.
我是怎么死的?
How does it happen?
你摔下马，然后撞到电篱笆
You get thrown from a horse into an electric fence.
什么? 洁西卡讨厌马
A what? Jessica hates horses.
经过这件事，她也不会喜欢电
After this, she's not gonna be crazy about electricity either.
请记住，你们要想象我穿着苏格兰裙
Now, remember, you have to imagine me in a kilt.
我想象你穿着短格子花呢衬衫和到膝的袜子
I can imagine you in a short plaid skirt and knee socks.
-你要开始讲秘密吗? -不
- You wanna start telling secrets? - No.
请记住…
Now, remember...
我还在学
...l'm still learning.
一，二，三，四!
One, two, three, four!
你们都知道这首歌，一起唱吧
You know the song. Sing along.
怎么样?
So?
-不 -不
- No. - No.
在妈妈的马鞍上动手脚是个超级好点子，佛莱德克
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse was brilliant, Fredrick.
电篱笆那个点子太妙了
And the electric fence, inspired.
谢谢你，亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
我不敢相信她真的死了
I can't believe she's really gone.
看看你的四周，一切都是我们的
Look around you. All of this is ours.
我可不那么认为
I don't think so.
你是谁?
Who are you?
怎么了?  笛娜
What's the matter, Dina?
你不认得你自己的…
Don't you recognize your own...
妈妈吗?
...mother?
停! 大家都演得很好，谢谢
Cut! That was great, everybody. Thank you.
那真的是太棒了
That was so wonderful!
我想你比我更适合演洁西卡
I think that you're a better Jessica than I ever was.
-喔，不 -当然不是，但你真的很棒
- Oh, no. - Of course not, but you were good.
谢谢
Thanks.
好消息，我找到新工作了
Good news. I got another job.
太棒了，是什么样的工作
Great. Hey, all right! What is it?
我要到瓜达拉哈拉（墨西哥西部城市）拍电影
A film in Guadalajara.
你是指那个机场?
The airport?
不，那是拉瓜迪亚机场
No, that's LaGuardia.
-我要去墨西哥 -哇
- This is Mexico. - Oh, wow.
你会去多久?
Well, how long will you be gone?
八个月
Eight months.
-那真的很久 -对，但你可以来看我
- That's a really long time. - Yeah, but you could come and visit.
我敢说你能在那里拥有几个地方
I bet that you could own a few places down there.
你知道的，或许我该先在那里买房子
Oh, you know, I should probably buy a place in the city first.
我刚了解你的意思，那…
And I just got what you meant. That is...
-那真的有难度 -真的很难
- That's a tricky one. - It's tricky.
乔伊，我真的要谢谢你
Joey, I really want to thank you.
你减少了我在困境中的痛苦
You made a very difficult time for me a little less painful.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你也是
You too.